<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on kasreti&#39;s crib</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on kasreti&#39;s crib</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Half-Consonants and the Evolution of Cosyran</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/rikascript-and-verbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/rikascript-and-verbs/</guid>
      
      <description>Over the course of the past two weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve been revamping my conscript (writing system): Isyaxé Kiryada. While teaching the script to my friends, I realized that a fatal flaw with the script was that even after previous updates, it was unable to express certain consonant clusters, such as in the phrase cosyran ka (note that c is pronounced like ch, and sy is pronounced like sh). But why? Why didn&amp;rsquo;t I just design the script to support such a basic feature of the language to begin with?</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>test post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 17:25:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/test-post/</guid>
      
      <description>hello welcome to michaelsof
i&amp;rsquo;ve uh yet to make a proper blog page check out the about section for now the new world order is here!!!</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>about</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Welcome to kasreti&amp;rsquo;s crib! This is basically where I&amp;rsquo;ll put any long ramblings I have &amp;ndash; but what should you expect here?
Linguistics and conlangs I do reading on my own about linguistics quite often, so I&amp;rsquo;ll put any new discoveries that I find cool here and share them. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to put more explainer notes around to clarify some terminology since 90% of the people reading this blog will have zero clue about linguistics.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
